The konpeito... are accumulating.
Kobato's wish has changed.
But the contract cannot be changed.
The contract to reach the place she wished to go to...
That's just like a curse now!
What's happening?
I must go to the place I should be at.
Goodbye.
Kobato.
How do I do this again?
The simplest things in life
end up being the most difficult.
I just want to smile when I'm happy
and sing a song whenever I please.
I was told, "Someday,
your dream will come true."
But when exactly will that be?
I can't wait that long!
I spread my arms
on the count of one two three
and gather all the light in the world.
Tell me,
isn't there something I can do?
Even if someone hurts my feelings,
I'll keep running toward the light.
Even if I trip, fall, and cry my eyes out, I still believe.
Although it may seem silly...
I believe in tomorrow.
Production
The Kobato Protection Group
...The Days That Follow.
Are you guys all right?
We're sorry.
Mama told us to come clean up the futon.
Futon?
Why was there a futon in an unoccupied room?
Oh!
Fujimoto carried it for us.
Kiyokazu, is your arm okay?
Yeah. It's already been a month after all.
I see. Thank you.
Mama, what's that?
Oh, I was thinking of searching for a new tenant...
That room's been empty since
before Fujimoto got here and all.
Without a tenant, even a room can get empty, you know?
Is that so?
Chitose, I'll air out that room every once in a while, so do you think we could keep it unoccupied for a bit?
How come?
Huh?
Oh... I'm sorry.
I just said something strange.
Kiyokazu!
It's been a while.
Is it true that you didn't go to the professor's seminar?
Yeah.
Don't you want to be a lawyer?
I've heard that lately you haven't even been taking notes anymore. What's the matter?
Nothing really.
You're kind of off.
It's like you've lost your drive or something.
Not really.
Well, you did lose something really important.
It's already been three months since it happened...
I'm sorry about the Nursery.
Oh... I wasn't really that worried about it.
I just...
Just?
Nevermind...
It's nothing.
Thank you.
I heard that the children were
worried about Yomogi Nursery...
So we all came to see it together!
Hey Fujimoto...
I was thinking of trying to start up Yomogi Nursery again.
Okiura said that this time, he'd do everything he could to help out.
That's great. I'm glad.
Thank you.
You do your best too, Fujimoto.
Huh?
I heard that you've been kind of down at school lately. I was worried.
Darn it, Domoto...
Once everything's set up again, let's all go on an outing together, okay?
Sure, let's all go...
Let's all?
Yes, all together.
Yay, outing!
Yup, that's right.
Where are we going?
I want to go too!
Of course. We'll all go together.
Right, Fujimoto?
Huh? Y-Yeah...
Yay, all together!
Fujimoto!
You're such a bully...
I'm sorry!
I'll do my best!
What the hell is this?
What's going on?
Why...
Why doesn't anyone remember her?
Excuse me!
Good morning.
It doesn't look like you're here to deliver the paper this time.
Yes, I remember her.
There isn't a single person who remembers her.
And yet, you do. Why?
Is that really what you want to ask about?
Is there not something else?
Please tell me.
When she disappeared, she said that she had to go to the place she should to be at.
What does that mean?
If you really want to know the truth, then please, somehow calmly listen to what I am about to tell you.
Do you understand?
Yeah.
A long time ago, because of another unfortunate incident with the human world, that girl lost her life.
Her life?
Kobato's wish...
...was to be reborn across time at the side of the person she loved.
That was her wish.
And in order to make it come true, she was put to the test...
and permitted to come down to this world.
She was granted only four seasons, and came with just a temporary soul.
Then she's now... already at that place?
That I don't know.
Throughout the long, long months and years, Shuichiro and I have had many sad partings.
Is Shuichiro that doctor?
Yes.
But you see, every time Shuichiro is reborn...
Yes, every time he is reborn, our hearts are called together,
and we cross each other's paths once again.
Even if we've lost all memory of our previous lives.
It's because we share the same soul.
With our souls as one, we will be called together again and again, as long as time continues.
Of that, I'm sure.
At that rate, who knows what would've happen if the factory's machines were impounded?
But everything's okay thanks to you, Mr. Fukita.
I'm glad things worked out.
Good luck with everything.
Thank you very much.
Oh, Fujimoto.
Yes?
You don't need to do this now, but make sure you take a look at the file on my desk.
I'm going away for a bit and there's
something I want you to take care of.
Right.
It's supposedly about property inheritance.
Mr. Fukita, who is this?
Oh, is this your first time seeing him, Mr. Yamaguchi?
It's been just about four years since he came to work at my firm.
Hello, this is Fukita Law Firm.
Even though he's still young, he's very on top of things.
Fujimoto, it's the courthouse clerk.
Coming.
It's about the client who passed away a few days ago.
Two years ago, because both his son and daughter-in-law had died,
he revised his will to allow his grandchild to be his inheritor.
But regarding the real estate,
because his family is an old one,
the boundaries on their grounds have become rather obscure.
I understand.
I will go there and take a look at the area tomorrow.
...flowers that bloom in springtime,
the endless skies of summer
are both brilliantly...
So you're from the law firm!
It's very nice to meet you.
It's very nice to meet you too.
Even if we've lost all memory of our previous lives.
Stop! Please stop!
You're my most important person, Fujimoto.
Up until now...
From now on... till the end of time.
The piano...
You're very good at it!
I'm sorry for playing it without asking first.
I don't know why, but somehow I know that song as well.
Isn't that strange?
Is that so?
Someone important to me sang that song for me in the past,
and I've always, always been looking for her.
I see.
I hope you'll be able to find her.
Yes.
Then, would it be all right for me to check the inside of your house?
Oh, yes!
And that's it.
I'll return to the office now and start the proceedings for succession.
Thank you very much!
And also, I need to return this to you.
Huh?
Konpeito?
And lastly... could you sing that song for me one more time?
Of course!
The flowers that bloom in springtime,
the endless skies of summer
are both brilliantly engraved into my heart.
Even when it rains and the windows are closed,
the overflowing light from my heart shines from...
Are you all right?
I get it now.
The place I wanted to go to...
The place where the person I
wanted to be with most was...
If I were able to meet that person once again,
this time, I wanted to make sure I could greet him with a smile...
But... it really is impossible for me, isn't it?
Kobato?
I'm home!
You've made me wait for so many years...
You're terribly late, you know.
Fujimoto!
Happiness or sadness,
I'll embrace all of it and continue walking forward.
They are what so strongly connect...
...my hands to yours.
Fall is by the waterfront, winter is hidden in the tips of branches.
There is limitless kindness in the depth of the world.
Each time night falls, let us offer up a prayer.
In the end, even though that idiot fulfilled his mission,
because he said he wanted to watch over that girl from the shadows and decided to stay in the human world,
we have no choice but to stay here and just grumble over our baumkuchen.
That we can welcome each coming day with peace.
Yeah.
Baumkuchen is delicious, isn't it?
Man...
A full 100 points to the mighty Ioryogi.
Guide me, O voice, so far, far away.
Like smiles...
Like songs...
The resonating sound of the wind.
Happiness or sadness,
I'll embrace all of it and continue walking forward.
They are what so strongly connect...
...my hands to yours.